Color Combination - The Challenge 

You recently had a state-of-the-art security system installed in your home. 
The master control panel requires a series of bi-colored chips to be placed 
end to end in a speciﬁc sequence in order to gain access. The security 
provider split up the chips and gave a random number to each of your family 
members. All of you must convene in order to assemble the chips and create 
the correct color combination. 


Programming Challenge
The access panel has a channel for the security chips. On each end of the 
channel is a colored marker. Chips are placed end to end such that the 
adjacent colors match and the starting and ending chips are color matched 
to the corresponding markers.  Write a program to see if the family has all 
the chips necessary to unlock the master control panel. 

Input 
The input consists of a single line indicating the beginning and ending marker 
colors followed by a series of chip deﬁnitions. All lines consist of a pair of 
color indicators; you may use integers, strings, or characters to represent 
each color. For our example purposes, we will use strings. 

Output 
If the combination cannot be achieved by using all of the chips once and only 
once, then report “Cannot unlock master panel”. If the combination can be 
achieved, then print the chips in the order required to unlock the master control. 


Examples 
Example - One
Input - blue, green,blue, yellow,red, orange,red, green,yellow, red,orange, purple
Output - Cannot unlock master panel

Example - Two
Input - blue, green,blue, yellow,red, oranger,red, green,yellow, red,orange, red
Output - blue, yellow,yellow, red,red, orange,orange, red,red, green